const QUESTIONS_ONE = [
  questionOne = {
    question: 'What is the capital of South Africa?',
    answers: ['Johannesburg', 'Cape Town', 'Pretoria'],
    correctAnswer: 'Pretoria'
  },
  questionTwo = {
    question: 'What is the longest river in USA?',
    answers: ['Danube', 'Mississippi', 'Dakota'],
    correctAnswer: 'Mississippi'
  },
  questionThree = {
    question: 'What is an axolotl?',
    answers: ['A species of salamander', 'A multi-axel vehicle', 'A bone in the human foot'],
    correctAnswer: 'A species of salamander'
  },
  questionFour = {
    question: 'In which Australian state is Darwin?',
    answers: ['Tasmania', 'Queensland', 'Western Australia', 'Northern Territory'],
    correctAnswer: 'Northern Territory'
  },
  questionFive = {
    question: 'What is a group of dolphins called?',
    answers: ['Pod', 'School', 'Herd'],
    correctAnswer: 'Pod'
  },
  questionSix = {
    question: 'Who won the most Academy Awards?',
    answers: ['Steven Spielberg', 'Walt Disney', 'James Cameron', 'Katherine Hepburn'],
    correctAnswer: 'Walt Disney'
  },
  questionSeven = {
    question: 'Who is the "King of the Gods" in Greek mythology?',
    answers: ['Apollo', 'Poseidon', 'Dionysus', 'Zeus'],
    correctAnswer: 'Zeus'
  },
  questionEight = {
    question: 'Clouds are caused by what?',
    answers: ['Evaporation', 'Melting ice crystals', 'Water vapour condensing'],
    correctAnswer: 'Water vapour condensing'
  },
  questionNine = {
    question: 'What pastry is used to make profiteroles?',
    answers: ['Choux', 'Filo', 'Flaky', 'Shortcrust'],
    correctAnswer: 'Choux'
  },
  questionTen = {
    question: 'The Blue Grotto is a spectacular sea cave on which island?',
    answers: ['Elba', 'Florence', 'Capri', 'Sardinia'],
    correctAnswer: 'Capri'
  },
];

const QUESTIONS_TWO = [
  questionOne = {
    question: 'Fish breathe through their?',
    answers: ['Gills', 'Nostrils', 'Skin', 'Fins'],
    correctAnswer: 'Gills'
  },
  questionTwo = {
    question: 'Why is the sky blue?',
    answers: ['Light reflects off the ocean', 'Blue light is scattered in all directions', 'Space is the colour blue'],
    correctAnswer: 'Blue light is scattered in all directions'
  },
  questionThree = {
    question: 'Which tree grows from an acorn?',
    answers: ['Ash', 'Oak', 'Pine', 'Spruce'],
    correctAnswer:'Oak' 
  },
  questionFour = {
    question: 'How many degrees are there in a circle?',
    answers: ['180', '45', '100', '360'],
    correctAnswer:'360' 
  },
  questionFive = {
    question: 'What or who was said Saint Patrick to have expelled from Ireland?',
    answers: ['Snakes', 'The English', 'Dragons', 'Druids'],
    correctAnswer:'Snakes' 
  },
  questionSix = {
    question: 'If you were in the city of Winnipeg, which Canadian province would you be in?',
    answers: ['New Foundland', 'Manitoba', 'Quebec', 'Alberta'],
    correctAnswer:'Manitoba' 
  },
  questionSeven = {
    question: 'Which element is there more of than any other in the Earths crust?',
    answers: ['Hydrogen', 'Iron', 'Oxygen'],
    correctAnswer:'Oxygen' 
  },
  questionEight = {
    question: 'What is the square root of 36?',
    answers: ['3', '12', '6'],
    correctAnswer:'6' 
  },
  questionNine = {
    question: 'Which two seas are connected by the Suez Canal?',
    answers: ['Mediterranean and Red Sea', 'Red and Arabian Sea', 'Mediterranean and Arabian Sea'],
    correctAnswer:'Mediterranean and Red Sea' 
  },
  questionTen = {
    question: 'In World War II, on what date did D-Day take place?',
    answers: ['June 6, 1944', 'June 5, 1944', 'June 6, 1945', 'May 6, 1944'],
    correctAnswer:'June 6, 1944' 
  },
]

const QUESTIONS_THREE = [
  questionOne = {
    question: 'In which decade did Roger Bannister run the worldâ€™s first recorded four minute mile?',
    answers: ['1940s', '1950s', '1960s'],
    correctAnswer: '1950s' 
  },
  questionTwo = {
    question: 'In a car, what does ABS stand for?',
    answers: ['Anti-lock Braking System', 'All Bearing System', 'Abrasive Boost Steering'],
    correctAnswer: 'Anti-lock Braking System'
  },
  questionThree = {
    question: `Why don't cows drink milk?`,
    answers: ['Because they lack toes', 'Because they would rather drink water', ],
    correctAnswer: 'Because they lack toes'
  },
  questionFour = {
    question: 'Bill Gates is known for his work in which non-profit organisation?',
    answers: ['Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation', 'Microsoft', 'UNESCO'],
    correctAnswer: 'Bill and Melinda Gates Foundation',
  },
  questionFive = {
    question: 'Which is the larger island; Greenland or Iceland?',
    answers: ['Greenland', 'Iceland'],
    correctAnswer: 'Greenland'
  },
  questionSix = {
    question: `What is the hardest tissue in a mammal's body?`,
    answers: ['Lip', 'Enamel', 'Aorta', 'Medulla'],
    correctAnswer: 'Enamel'
  },
  questionSeven = {
    question: 'An endangered species is at risk of extinction?',
    answers: ['True', 'False'],
    correctAnswer: 'True'
  },
  questionEight = {
    question: 'Seaweed is from what?',
    answers: ['Algae', 'Fungus', 'Fish', 'Bacteria'],
    correctAnswer: 'Algae'
  },
  questionNine = {
    question: 'Which landlocked country is completly surrounded by one country?',
    answers: ['Lesotho', 'Luxembourg', 'Burkina Faso'],
    correctAnswer: 'Lesotho'
  },
  questionTen = {
    question: 'The Canadian city of Toronto used to be known as which British city',
    answers: ['Bristol', 'York', 'London', 'Glasgow'],
    correctAnswer: 'York'
  }
]